Handel Olivier Baptiste

FullStack Developer

CONTACT

baptistecoding10@gmail.com 💌

(438)-923-7308

Montreal, QC

/in/holivierbaptiste

github.com/GitBap

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I want to acquire experience and knowledge in computer development, language programming and anything else regarding technology. Knowing that I must stay up to date to remain in this field, it encourages me to start and pursue my career in web development or cybersecurity.

EDUCATION

Baccalaureate cumulatively in management and security of information systems
2021 - current
Professional Development
Certificate in Full Stack JavaScript
Development
2023 - 2023

SKILLS

JavaScript (ES6, React, Node.js) SQL (PostgreSQL, MySQL), C++, Java, PHP, XML, C, C#, HTML/ CSS, Agile/Scrum

TOOLS

Npm, Yarn, Git, Bash, Powershell, Postman, Insomnia, Xampp, Draw.io, Oxygen xml

CURRENTLY LEARNING

TypeScript

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance work

Phara

Current

- Met the client to understand the goals and requirements for the website
- Designed the website's layout and functionality.
- Established the languages, frameworks, and tolls to build the website.
- Working on the responsive design and the back-end development of the website.

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

hobaptiste.netlify.app/

HANDEL OLIVIER BAPTISTE

Montreal, QC *Phone number :* (438) 923-7308

Spoken Languages

• French, English

Languages Written

■ French, English

Career Objective

■ To gain work experience and leverage my skills and abilities

Specific Skills

- Motivated
- Resourceful
- Efficient
- Team player
- Respectful
- Independent

Études

2012-2014	Collège Saint-Jean Vianney	
2014-2017	Collège Citoyen	High School Diploma
2017 – 2018	Collège Montmorency	Studies in Humanities
2019 - 2021	Collège Lionel-Groulx	Associate Degree in Humanities
2021 – present	Université de Montréal	Bachelor's degree in Information Systems Management and Security
2022 – 2023	McGill University	McGill SCS Professional Development Certificate in Full Stack JavaScript Development

Work Experience

pallet jack or stomers	Picking and pack Operating a pall forklift Assisting custon Shelving produc	Transbec	July 2022 – September 2022
supplies es to the store varehouse	Unloading and I trucks Organizing supp Moving supplies to Cleaning the wareh Processing custome	Maison Corbeille - Warehouse	July 2021 – December 2021
ore sections omer needs	Sorting clothes Supervising store se Assisting customer Organizing clothes	Urban Behavior – Place Rosemère	July 2019 – September 2019
)	Organizing clo		

November 2018 – Ma7 2019	Funtropolis – Amusement Center	•	Supervising attractions Cleaning party rooms Cleaning tables Changing and emptying trash bins
July 2018 – September 2018	SescoSchool Service	•	Packing and labeling school supplies in boxes
April 2016	Collections Unimage Laval	•	Assisting customers in choosing school uniforms Organizing and shelving clothes Providing information to

Involvement

- Volunteer at College Citoyen Open House (2017)
- English tutoring at College Citoyen (2017)
- Volunteer at the Champ Fleury Race, Laval (2013)
- Volunteer at Le Portail Church in Laval (2013 to 2019)
- Volunteer at Le Repos Church (2020 to now)

Interests and Hobbies

- Sports (basketball, soccer, volleyball, football, combat sports & weightlifting)
- Travel
- Reading
- Music
- Movies